[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "How does the WriteWiseAI platform work?",
        "answer": "WriteWiseAI is an AI-powered platform designed to help IELTS test-takers improve their writing skills. Users can submit essays for rating, receive personalized feedback, and track your progress. Simply sign up, log in, write or upload your essay, and have it rated to receive your score and individualized insights and resommendations."
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How does WriteWiseAI score and analyze essays?",
        "answer": "WriteWiseAI uses advanced artificial intelligence algorithms to accurately score and analyze essays based on the specific criteria of IELTS writing exams. The AI evaluates Task Achievement/Response, Cohesion and Coherence, Lexical Resource, and Grammatical Range and Accuracy. Then it provides your score, and personalized feedback and recommendations to help you improve your writing skills."
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "How long does it take to get feedback on my essay?",
        "answer": "WriteWiseAI provides feedback on your essay almost instantly. Within seconds of submitting your essay, you will receive a comprehensive analysis, personalized feedback, and targeted recommendations to help you improve"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Can I use WriteWiseAI for both General and Academic IELTS writing tasks?",
        "answer": "Absolutely! WriteWiseAI supports Task 1 General, Task 1 Academic, and Task 2 essay types, allowing you to practice and improve your writing skills for any IELTS test format."
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How do I pay for WriteWiseAI services?",
        "answer": "To use our Pay-as-you-Go system, after signing up and logging in, navigate to the \"Wallet\" section in your user panel. Then, select a payment model , and complete the payment process. You can then use your wallet to access rating, analysis and personalized feedback and recommendations."
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How accurate are the AI-generated essay ratings?",
        "answer": "WriteWiseAI uses advanced AI technology to analyze your essays based on the official IELTS criteria. While our system is highly accurate and reliable, it's important to remember that AI-generated ratings may not perfectly match those of human examiners. We suggest a “between-rater” difference of half a band score to be considered. Nonetheless, our ratings serve as a valuable tool for understanding your current writing proficiency and tracking your progress."
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Is my personal information and essay data secure on WriteWiseAI?",
        "answer": "Yes, we take data privacy and security very seriously. WriteWiseAI uses industry-standard encryption and security measures to protect your personal information and essay data. We do not share your information with third parties without your consent."
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Can I use WriteWiseAI for other types of English exams or general writing improvement?",
        "answer": "WriteWiseAI is specifically designed to help users prepare for IELTS writing exam. However, the feedback and recommendations provided by our platform can also be beneficial for general writing improvement and other types of English exams that involve essay writing."
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What payment methods does WriteWiseAI accept?",
        "answer": "WriteWiseAI accepts a variety of payment methods using Stripe and Nowpayment’s secure payment services. For ease of use, we offer localized pricing plans in different currencies and cryptocurrency."
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": " What is the AI-powered topic generator, and how can I use it?",
        "answer": "The AI-powered topic generator is a feature available in both free and paid plans that generates essay topics for users to practice writing. It helps users by providing fresh, relevant topics tailored to the specific exam type (IELTS General Task 1, IELTS Academic Task1, and IELTS Task 2 writing). To use the topic generator, simply choose the exam type and generate a new topic to practice writing."
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Can I access WriteWiseAI on my mobile device?",
        "answer": "Yes, WriteWiseAI is designed to be accessible on both desktop and mobile devices. Our platform is optimized for a seamless user experience across various screen sizes and devices, allowing you to practice and improve your IELTS writing skills anytime, anywhere."
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Can I get a refund if I'm not satisfied with the service?",
        "answer": " We strive to provide the best possible experience for our users. If you're not satisfied with the services provided by WriteWiseAI, please reach out to our customer support team.We'll work with you to address your concerns and, if necessary, discuss the possibility of a refund on a case-by-case basis."
    }
]